Guide to the Billboard Photograph Collection ca 1918-1934 PR 5
New-York Historical Society
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60287)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60288)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60289)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60290)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60291)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60292)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60293)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60294)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, September 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60295)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 28, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60296)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60297)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60298)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60299)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60300)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60301)
- 5th Ave & 42nd View along front of New York Public Library; no billboards, September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60302)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60303)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60304)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60305)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60306)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60307)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60308)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60309)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60310)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60311)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60312)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60313)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60314)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60315)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60316)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60317)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60318)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 27, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60319)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 27, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60320)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 27, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60321)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60322)
- 6th Ave & 27th, November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60323)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60324)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60325)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60326)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60327)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60328)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave, November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60329)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60330)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60331)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60332)
- 6th Ave & 27th, December 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60333)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 14, Item 60334)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60335)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60336)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60337)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, December 29, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60338)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 29, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60339)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60340)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60341)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 30, 1931 (Box 15, Item 60342)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 16, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60343)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 16, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60344)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 16, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60345)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60346)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60347)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60348)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60349)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60350)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60351)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60352)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60353)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 18, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60354)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60355)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60356)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60357)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Two large telescopes and crowds in front of billboards, February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60358)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60359)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60360)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60361)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60362)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60363)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60364)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60365)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60366)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60367)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60368)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60369)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave, May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60370)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave, May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60371)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60372)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60373)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 27, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60374)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60375)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60376)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, May 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60377)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60378)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60379)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60380)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60381)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60382)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60383)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60384)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, June 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60385)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60386)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), June 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60387)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60388)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60389)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60390)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60391)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60392)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60393)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60394)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60395)
- 6th Ave & 27th, October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60396)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60397)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60398)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60399)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by Genreal Outdoor Adv. Co., October 31, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60400)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60401)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 15, Item 60402)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60403)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60404)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60405)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60406)
- 6th Ave & 47th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60407)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60408)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 29, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60409)
- 6th Ave & 27th, November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60410)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., November 30, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60411)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60412)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60413)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60414)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60415)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60416)
- 6th Ave & 27th, December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60417)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60418)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60419)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 31, 1932 (Box 16, Item 60420)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60421)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60422)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 30, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60423)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Realty Adv. & Supply Co., c. 1920 (Box 16, Item 60424)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack and Co., c. 1921 (Box 16, Item 60425)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 21, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60426)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60427)
- 6th Ave & 27th, April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60428)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60429)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60430)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60431)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60432)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60433)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60434)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60435)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60436)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60437)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60438)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60439)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60440)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60441)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60442)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60443)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60444)
- 6th Ave & 27th NEGATIVE DESTROYED 6/29/88, June 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60445)
- NEGATIVE DESTROYED 9/97 (Box 16, Item 60446)
- NEGATIVE DESTROYED 3/25/93 due to acetate deterioration (Box 16, Item 60447)
- NEGATIVE DESTROYED 3/25/93 due to acetate deterioration (Box 16, Item 60448)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave NEGATIVE DESTROYED 6/29/88, June 29, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60449)
- does not exist? No note re. its possible destruction (Box 16, Item 60450)
- NEGATIVE DESTROYED 7/93 (Box 16, Item 60451)
- does not exist? No note re. its possible destruction (Box 16, Item 60452)
- NEGATIVE DESTROYED 7/93 (Box 16, Item 60453)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60454)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60455)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60456)
- 6th Ave & 27th, July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60457)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 16, Item 60458)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 17, Item 60459)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1933 (Box 17, Item 60460)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60461)
- 6th Ave & 27th, January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60462)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60463)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60464)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60465)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60466)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60467)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60468)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., January 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60469)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60470)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60471)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox, May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60472)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60473)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60474)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60475)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and R. C. Maxwell Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60476)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60477)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., May 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60478)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60479)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60480)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60481)
- 6th Ave & 27th, June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60482)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60483)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60484)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60485)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60486)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 30, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60487)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60488)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60489)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60490)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60491)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60492)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60493)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60494)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60495)
- 6th Ave & 27th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., July 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60496)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60497)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60498)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60499)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60500)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60501)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60502)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60503)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60504)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60505)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60506)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60507)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60508)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60509)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60510)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60511)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60512)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September 29, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60513)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 31 (Box 17, Item 60514)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60515)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60516)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60517)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60518a)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60518b)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60519)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60520)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60521)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60522)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60523)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1934 (Box 17, Item 60524)